funnywow.com 2016-12-25

# Funnywow - Make funny photos and pictures online. Apply funny photo effects to your pictures with easy editing tool. try it free! - Privacy policy

## Privacy policy

Last Updated: Nov 9, 2009

This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how Funnywow, ("we", "us") collect and use the information you provide to us through our website at www.funnywow.com (the "Site") and our other services, and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our services. We do update our Privacy Policy from time to time without notice, so please check back periodically. 

By accessing and using the Site or services owned and/or operated by Funywow (the "Services"), you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Services.

### Collected Information

When you visit our website, you do so anonymously. We do not collect personal information. We do keep a log of your IP address to give us an idea of which parts of our website you visit and how long you spent visiting a particular page. We do not however, link your IP address to anything personally identifiable to any unique user. The other information that is automatically provided to us is the type of computer and operating system you use, the type of browsers you use, and the website from which you linked to us. Your browser supplies us with this information and you can not be identified from this information.

### Email Information

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we many retain the content of your email message together with your email address and our response.

### Cookies

  * We many use cookies from time to time. Cookies enable a website to tailor information presented to you based on your browsing preferences. We may use cookies to personalize web pages and access during your return visits.
  * Funnywow may also use cookies to track your visit to our website in order to collect aggregated data.
  * However, this information will only be used for analytical purposes and will not be limited to the minimum necessary to perform the analysis. If you do not want us to deploy cookies in your browser, you can set your browser to reject cookies or to notify you when a website tries to put a cookie in your browser software. Rejecting cookies may affect your ability to use of some of the services at our website.
  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

### Disclosures of Personal Information

We respect your privacy, including the privacy of your information and your pictures. We will not disclose any of your information without your permission unless:

  *  **Assignment.** We reserve the right to transfer Personal Information to a new entity or third party as part of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, sale of some or all of our assets, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business or assets. 
  * **Law Enforcement.** We may disclose Personal Information in the following situations as we believe to be appropriate. (a) under applicable law; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to governmental requests, including requests from law enforcement and regulatory authorities; (d) to enforce our terms and conditions; (e) to protect our operations; (f) to protect the rights, privacy, safety or property of us, you or others; and (g) to permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.
  *  **Third Party Service Providers.** We may share Personal Information with third parties to allow such third parties to provide you with the products, services and information that you have requested.

### Security

We try to have reasonable security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or data storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, although we strive to protect Personal Information about you, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us through or in connection with the Services or that is stored by us. You acknowledge and agree that any information you transmit through the Services or upload for storage in connection with the Services is so transmitted or stored at your own risk. Please notify us of the problem by contacting us in accordance with Section "Contact Us" below.

### Third Party Sites

Our website may contain links to third party websites. These linked sites are not under our control and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the contents of any such linked site, or any link contained in any linked site. The inclusion of a link on the Site does not imply endorsement of the linked site by us. If you provide any Personal Information through any such third party website, your transaction will occur on such third party's website and the Personal Information you provide will be collected by, and controlled by the privacy policy of, that third party. We recommend that you familiarize yourself with the privacy policies and practices of any such third parties.

### Changes and Notifications

We reserve the right to modify our Privacy Policy at any time. If our Privacy Policy changes, the revised policy will be posted on the Site and we will change the 'Last Updated' date to reflect the date of the modification. Please check back periodically. Any changes to our Privacy Policy will become effective upon our posting of the revised Privacy Policy on the Services.
